Adriano Mazzucco

416-716-4963 | adrianommazzucco@gmail.com | https://adrianomazzucco.github.io/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY/MOTIVATION

Creating engaging memorable experiences for gamers of all ages has motivated me to pursue my career as a Gameplay/AI programmer. I am Software Engineer with 8+ years experience developing efficient object oriented code. I am passionate about developing modular game-play code and tools to allow for easy implementation and iteration. I enjoy working with designers to get their perspective and work as a team to bring their vision to life. My team finished our competitive MOBA/RTS asymmetrical PVP game, during this our team worked as a cohesive unit to create the game in only 4 months. I recently was awarded 2nd place in Ubisoft NEXT for my project, in which I made my own 3D math library and ECS game engine. Both of these projects can be found on my portfolio website.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: C++, C#/Unity, C

Software Architecture: Entity Component System, Mixin Design Pattern **Game AI**: Mini-Max, A* Path-finding, Behavior Trees, Steering Behaviors

Graphics: OpenGL, HLSL, GLSL, SFML

Soft Skills: Motivated, Problem Solving, Teamwork, Creativity, Time Management

ACHIEVEMENTS

2nd Place Ubisoft Next programming competition

2023

- Implemented ECS engine over one month using C++
- Created 3D math library to create a 3D game using a 2D graphics API provided by Ubisoft
- Built a Bomber-Man inspired Game in one weekend

Toronto Hydro Student award

2018/2019

 Awarded to the student group that created a web application that could be used by Toronto Hydro in a real life application

Ryerson Capstone Design Project Excellence Award Gold

2019

• Awarded to best capstone project for Ryerson Engineering

EDUCATION

Sheridan Oakville, Canada

Graduate Certificate, Game Development Advanced Programming September 2022 - August 2023

- Game engine architecture
- Implemented Entity Component system architecture in C++
- Worked with Unity engine and C# to implement Gameplay, UI and AI
- A* path-finding, Behavior trees, Mini-Max with pruning, Finite State Machines

Toronto Metropolitan University

Toronto, Canada

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Engineering

September 2015 - June 2019

- Advanced Algorithms, Software Architecture, Image Processing
- Networking, Network Security
- Digital Systems Engineering, Database Systems, Embedded programming
- Linear Algebra, Calculus

EXPERIENCE

Gameplay Programmer

May 2023 - August 2023

Always Snacking Studios - Sheridan

Toronto, Canada

- Working with a team to make a RTS game for our capstone project
- Implementing the Mixin design pattern to build a data-driven system to create modular gameplay features
- The Project can be found here: https://always-snacking-studios.itch.io/the-big-vs-them-all

Data Analyst

May 2020 - August 2020

Kubra Toronto, Canada

- Registered print jobs through proprietary Kubra software.
- Data validation of all registered print orders
- Made changes to code to resolve errors using C++ and visual basic

Software Engineer

September 2018 - April 2019

Ryerson University

Toronto, Canada

- · Developed a cloud based power-flow assessment tool as my capstone project
- · Worked with JavaScript to create front end for power flow tool
- Published a technical document with IEEE: https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/9025140

Software Engineer

September 2016 - December 2016

Stock Render

Toronto, Canada

- Work with startup team to develop stock processing website
- · Developed JavaScript algorithms to analyze and organize data from a SQL database

Office Assistant

July 2012 - August 2019

Toronto Catholic District School-board

Toronto, Canada

- Took student attendance, called parents of absent students
- Handled any issues that arose at the school

Physics tutor

July 2012 - August 2019

Private tutor Toronto, Canada

• Tutored high-school physics, helped students prepare for exams